http://www.tonalvision.com/about/privacy-policy.html

PRIVACY POLICY
It is Tonal Vision’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.  If you have questions about our use of your personal data please This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Tonal Vision collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Tonal Vision’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Tonal Vision’s visitors use our website.
From time to time, Tonal Vision may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of our website. Tonal Vision also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blog. Tonal Vision only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that we use and disclose personal information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses may be visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personal Information
Purchases from Tonal Vision's store require additional personal information to process orders.  In each case, Tonal Vision collects only the information necessary to allow us to complete and ship your purchase.  We disclose that information only to employees who need it for order processing.  Your actual payment transaction is completed on PayPal's site, and PayPal communicates your order to us via email.  We do not have access to your credit card information, and information about the transaction is not stored on our server.
Protection of Personal Information
Tonal Vision will not not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Tonal Vision uses cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of Tonal Vision's website, and their website access preferences. Tonal Vision visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website.
Tonal Vision has embedded YouTube and Vimeo videos on our site.
When a visitor plays a video, these video players use cookies and similar tracking technologies to enhance the player experience and to understand how people are using them.
We have no control over these third party cookies.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not intentionally collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Tonal Vision may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. Tonal Vision encourages visitors to check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Change log:
Initial version of policy issued:  2/11/2012
Updated to reflect YouTube and Vimeo player cookies:  4/17/2019
Note of appreciation:  We borrowed some of the structure and initial wording of this policy from Automattic who graciously made their privacy policy available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license.  We also used information from FreePrivacyPolicy.com.
About Us
Who We Are
Jacquie Greff
Kraig Greff
Contact Us
Fast Facts
Awards
Clients
1607 Lancaster St.,
Baltimore, MD 21231 •
410.675.0591 •
800.729.3905 •
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
